margauxny.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy – Margaux

Welcome to Margaux’s website (hereinafter the “Site”). This Privacy Policy informs you of our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information you may provide or Margaux New York, LLC (hereinafter “Margaux”) may collect via the Site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to the Site. We respect your privacy, and we are committed to protecting your personal information.

By accessing and using the Site, you agree with the terms of the Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Margaux reserves the right to modify the Privacy Policy, at its discretion and without notice to you. Please review the Privacy Policy from time to time to stay up to date with any changes.

For users outside of the United States: This Site is intended for use only in the United States. Margaux does not represent that the content of this Site is appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you are an EU user or non-U.S. user of the Site, by visiting the Site and providing us with information, you acknowledge and agree that your Personal Information may be processed for the purposes identified in the Privacy Policy. In addition, your Personal Information may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the U.S., where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country. By providing your information, you consent to such transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy.

1\. Collection of information. The Site collects information that may personally identify you (such as your name, address, email address, phone number or other related data) only when you provide such information directly to Margaux. In some cases, the Site collects information that personally identifies third parties if you purchase and ship a product to a third party.

The Site also collects certain non-personal information that does not identify any individual user, such as IP (internet protocol) address, ISP (internet service provider), the web browser used to visit the Site, the time the Site was visited, which web pages were visited on the Site and other anonymous usage data.

The Site collects information regarding transactions that take place on the Site, such as details about a purchased or returned product and the date and place of purchase or return.

The Site may also collect non-personal information through the use of cookies and navigational data:  
A “cookie” is a bit of information that a website sends to your web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences.  
A “web beacon” is used to monitor your behavior when you visit a website, such as recording whether you have viewed a certain webpage.  
“Session” cookies are temporary bits of information that are erased once you exit your web browser window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on websites and to collect aggregate statistical information.

“Navigational data” (“log files”, “server logs” and “clickstream” data) are used for system management, improvement of the Site content, market research, and communication of information to visitors.  
Margaux respects the privacy of children, and does not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not use the Site, or submit any personal information through this Site.

2\. Use of information. We will not sell, share or rent your personal information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.  
We may use your personal information and non-personal information for internal purposes, including to:  
Provide the products and services requested;  
Improve the content of this Site;  
Customize the website to your preferences;  
Communicate to you (if requested); and  
Improve and facilitate marketing and research.  
We may also share information in certain circumstances:  
With vendors and other service providers who need access to such information in order to complete work on our behalf;  
When required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process;  
To protect the rights, property and safety of Margaux or any third party;  
With your consent; and  
In connection with any proposed merger, sale of company assets, financing, change of ownership or transfer of all or a portion of Margaux’s business to another company.

3\. Security of information. Margaux employs reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. However, you should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. It is your responsibility to safeguard the password and identification assigned to you. While Margaux strives to protect personal information, Margaux cannot and does not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Site, and you do so at your own risk.

4\. Third-party advertisements and websites. The Site may contain links to websites operated by third parties. If you use these links to access third-party websites, you will leave this Site. Margaux does not endorse any such linked third-party websites and assumes no responsibility for the content of any third-party website. These third parties may use cookies or other technologies to collect information about your use of this Site.

5\. Questions and comments. If you have any questions or comments regarding the Privacy Policy or any other content of this Site, please contact us.
